(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World=
(From the French film Amélie)
Without you, to whom can I share the beautiful moments?
(Paris,)
(this romantic capital hailed worldwide)
(as the City of Light.)
(Every tender dream of romance)
(can find its place in this city.)
(The Seine River flows gently
through the city.)
(Plane trees on both banks sway softly
in the breeze.)
(Cruise boats
glide under the Pont Alexandre III,)
(ripples scattering reflections
of historic buildings.)
(Next,)
(let's roam)
(this romantic city)
(with our romantic partners.)
=EP05 Part 2: Bonjour Paris=
(Paris, Sweet Beyond Words)
(Paris, France)
Welcome to
Paris, the City of Romance.
A romantic journey
full of unknowns and surprises
is about to begin.
(Song Qian)
Please take your romantic token and head to the designated spot
to unlock today's
French-style Romantic Journey together.
It feels like a dating variety show.
Okay, I'll set off right now to find
my romantic partner.
Looking forward to it.
My impression of Paris
is that it's
the City of Romance.
Yes, it seems like lots of
love stories unfold in Paris.
How should I put it?
A silent devotion.
(What do you think
is the most romantic thing?)
I won't flaunt
my kindness to you outwardly.
Does my partner know it's me?
He doesn't know it's me, right?
So we all
work in pairs today
and need to find our own partners
by ourselves, right?
I'd most love to pair up
with Honglei.
I think Honglei can
protect me very well.
Looking forward to
our romantic encounter.
I think it's Yuwen.
We can make a bet.
If I win,
I get to pick the guests
for the next season.
(Already had a plan)
You always pick young guests.
I'll pick some
old guys.
Old guys and old ladies.
(Just thinking about it makes me happy)
I think romantic encounters
are meant for strangers.
When you turn around, it's like...
Ah, it's you!
It's you!
Then the two say "hello" to each other.
This kind of romance...
This is a real encounter.
If I turn around
and it's someone I know very well,
someone I've known for over ten years,
well,
you'd just go,
"Oh, it's you."
It isn't romantic.
Lin Yi and Wen, right?
Well,
the three of us always
hang out and eat together.
I don't know if it's romantic or not,
but it's a bit wasteful.
Let's see who gets this lucky.
Let's go.
Meet your romantic partner.
Work together to finish tasks,
paying tribute
to classic French romantic films.
I truly believe I will
meet my destined person here.
Where's my partner?
Are you my romantic partner?
Which side is she coming from?
I don't think it's that way.
It should be this way.
Yes.
A man.
I'm not.
It's really you.
It's you!
This is so mysterious.
It's really you.
We're quite matching today.
(We match perfectly)
Hello.
Let's meet up.
Then who were you thinking of?
I thought it was Yuwen.
Today, you're my romantic partner.
That's great, Yuning.
(Romantic partners have gathered.
The tribute mission is about to begin)
(Tribute to La Boum)
(Tribute to Before Sunset)
Do you believe that one day
Notre-Dame de Paris
will vanish?
This site once housed another church
long ago.
Right here.
So comfortable.
I've never tried this before.
Really?
I've already forgotten
how beautiful Paris is.
Actually,
being a tourist is quite nice.
(Tribute to Amélie)
Give me one...
We have
steamed lamb, steamed bear paw,
steamed deer tail,
roasted duck, roasted chick,
and roasted goose.
Which one would you like?
Would you prefer chicken or duck?
Skip the duck, though.
Just get a burger, please.
Okay, as you wish.
Okay, this little bear is for you.
Okay, thanks.
(Tribute to Léon: The Professional)
Listen.
Don't be so silly all day long,
or I'll punch you,
got it?
Yep.
If I were you,
I wouldn't be so unprofessional.
There are rules in this business.
Yep.
Can you stop saying "yep"?
Very good.
(Romantic Paris, Depart Now)
Are you cold?
I'm fine.
What's this?
Is this the Seine River?
The Seine River.
The Seine River Banks.
These are Île Saint-Louis
and Île de la Cité.
So this is the bank of Seine River.
Yes.
So happy.
So comfortable.
Walking casually on the streets
of Paris feels surreal.
Really.
Naiwen.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I'm your guide for today.
(Zu Lishu, Official docent of French museums)
Hello.
Okay.
I always thought this tower was black,
turns out it's brown.
Let's take a photo, guys.
Let's take one.
Three, two.
Didn't you want to buy souvenirs?
Where?
Look ahead.
Is that it over there?
Why are you buying souvenirs here?
Where else would you get them
if not under the Eiffel Tower?
Beijing also has this.
That World Park.
Have you been there?
I haven't.
I have.
Right next to it
is the Leaning Tower of Pisa.
So huge.
(Suddenly started raining)
Big raindrops are falling hard.
When they smack your skin,
it hurts a bit.
These big raindrops.
(Paris Today: Showers turning to hail)
As long as I move fast enough,
(Yuning's Rain-Avoiding Method)
it won't hit me.
The thunder is so loud.
Let's hurry up.
It's really not working.
It's getting heavier.
Hurry!
Run a few steps!
Don't wait anymore!
Hurry!
(The rain is getting heavier)
Coming!
Hurry!
I think it's
pretty fun.
What's this?
Welcome to Paris.
This is a bit fun.
Very exciting.
(Wow The World)
It's stopped raining now.
The clouds outside are so beautiful.
A rainbow appeared.
So big!
What a huge rainbow!
The sun is out.
After the rain,
the tower looks much cleaner.
It thundered and poured
for a moment just now.
Indeed.
We now officially welcome
Song Qian,
an all-around ACE
with unparalleled singing
and dancing skills.
(All-around ACE,
excellent in both singing and dancing)
Welcome!
This title feels way over the top
for me.
Welcome, everyone, to Paris.
This morning, everyone
found your romantic partner.
Now, let's hear your thoughts.
Are you satisfied
with your partner?
(Very satisfied)
I...
He must be the least satisfied one.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
(Silence speaks louder than words here)
Then this isn't enough, right?
This one.
(Double dissatisfaction)
This is the one.
Hard Evidence team.
How to say?
(Satisfied and confident)
Ready to compete in France, right?
Straight to Cannes.
Xingxu.
What scene did you perform?
Before Sunset.
Yes.
We have great chemistry today.
(In-sync siblings)
We're both dressed
in red.
And...
Yes.
We didn't discuss it at all.
Why are you wearing red?
Why red?
Such a coincidence.
We didn't discuss it at all.
We are talking about acting.
Not clothes.
Now we're in France, and we need
to talk about outfits, right?
Capital of Art.
That's right.
It felt incredible.
I stood on the street
holding a balloon,
waiting for my partner
under overcast skies.
But the second Lin Yi showed up,
the sun suddenly
broke through the clouds.
It cleared up.
Still not about acting.
Weather.
Clothing.
Balloon.
It's very much like when we evaluate
someone's acting skills,
we just
simply say he is a good person.
What about the plot?
I don't know.
Anyway, we two are definitely...
The upper half and the lower half
have totally different styles.
Yes.
Aren't your heights a perfect match?
Look at the shoes he's wearing today.
I feel like these shoes
make me look 2 meters tall today.
We can perform it one more time.
Very emotional music.
Let's hug first.
Then like this.
(I think it's so beautiful)
The upper half looks elegant,
but look at the lower half...
You.
What even is this posture?
Like this.
The upper part is elegant,
but the lower part
looks a bit awkward and lewd.
Lin Yi, you really don't know
how to read the room.
Take off your shoes.
If that's not enough,
take off your socks.
I'm afraid it will turn into
a biological weapon.
(So thoughtful)
No worry, I'll wash your socks for you.
(Uncle Sock's laundry service)
Nai has your back.
It's a series.
I made my fortune by washing socks.
So I own every property
around this part of Paris now.
Just by washing socks?
Yes.
(Top Sock Duke)
To the French,
whispering sweet nothings
and sharing private thoughts
close to someone's ears
is the ultimate romance.
The French language itself
is perfect for murmurs,
known as the language of love.
Absolutely impossible.
I don't agree at all.
I can speak French.
Its uvular trill and uvular sounds
can crush all sense of romance.
No, it's not.
I think the reason it feels romantic
is that many pronunciations
require you to pout your lips.
Don't you think so?
(Unique insight)
For example,
saying "hello".
Look.
Bonjour.
And...
Yes.
So romantic.
What I'm about to say is
"Love conquers all".
Honglei.
Scattered showers.
Why are there sudden showers here?
It's not suitable to say this too close.
(Brushing off negative remarks)
My pronunciation is absolutely perfect.
Is his pronunciation correct?
(French translator)
Come on.
No, you say it once.
And you translate it into Chinese.
Don't tell us the Chinese meaning first,
just say it directly.
Look at her expression.
No.
You didn't say it like that just now.
Wait a moment.
(Deeply hurt, absolutely impossible,
let me be alone)
Say it again.
Right?
Wait a moment.
It's like this.
(Emergency control)
You aren't familiar with ancient French prose, right?
(Pull back)
Ready to use force.
It means to conquer or defeat something.
Yes.
Love conquers all.
It's love, right?
Yes.
Love conquers all.
Love conquers...
Yes, all.
He led the translator step by step
to get the correct answer.
How dare you coach
a professional French translator?
Impressive.
Guided teaching.
It's not that my pronunciation
isn't standard.
(Speaking up for myself)
This is just
from classical French prose, okay?
No.
You're already...
Don't touch me.
(Completely triggered)
He's getting agitated.
They don't...
Two expressions.
Wait a moment.
They don't have this.
Come on.
Amélie.
Stop playing.
Okay, sit.
Sit down.
(Catch you off guard)
Just now...
That heavy rain.
Next up, we'll play a game
perfectly fitting
the French linguistic vibe,
Whisper Word Guessing.
Okay.
Pick one romantic partner duo.
One player wears headphones
and describes the word,
while the other player guesses the word.
The round is limited to 5 minutes.
During the guessing session,
the other six members wear blindfolds
and catch this pair inside the venue.
If either member is caught,
eliminate the whole pair right now.
During this process,
the catchers can also buzz in
based on the description.
A correct buzz-in answer
will void the current word right away.
The winning pair can enjoy
delicate, romantic French desserts.
Paris, sweet beyond words.
It's totally worth scrambling for.
Okay.
We all understand the rules, right?
Understood.
Come on.
Who goes first?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
To be fair, okay?
Then I'll do it.
I never lose at rock-paper-scissors.
Come on.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Paper, paper, paper, scissors)
Okay, I win.
Nice.
I never lose at rock-paper-scissors.
Come on.
(Beaming with joy)
Okay.
Like this.
(Sneaky Li Naiwen is here)
The winner goes first.
Okay?
Okay.
The winner goes first.
Come on.
(Wry smile)
It's fine.
His feelings are hurt.
(In that case)
Wait a moment.
I think this is unfair.
Come on.
Raise your hands
if you agree
that Naiwen and Fei go first.
Wait. No.
Wait.
Everything's messed up.
The order is messed up.
You suggested it.
Okay.
Very good.
Very smart.
I give up.
You give up?
Okay, let's go.
Listen. We'll get
a landslide victory.
Come on.
Who describes and who guesses?
I'll describe.
(Describer: Guo Jingfei, Guesser: Li Naiwen)
Because your comprehension is better.
(Is that so?)
Okay.
Fine.
Give me the card.
(Super strong comprehension)
Fei describes, and you guess.
That works too.
I don't get it.
Come on.
(Topic: A Chinese Ghost Story)
(4 characters)
(Identifying by sound)
Bro, your clothes are very noisy.
(On tiptoe)
(Run first, talk later)
(Wait for me)
I can hear sounds from my side.
Who's this?
This is me.
Who?
Me.
(Please wait for me)
What do you mean?
No, sounds are coming in here.
Movie.
(Warning: Close proximity)
(Split up)
(Reuniting again)
What movie?
Who?
No, he ran too fast.
Who's this?
(Struggling hard)
(Gripping tightly)
Fei.
(Guo Jingfei is caught, Mission over)
We've caught Fei.
(Not giving up)
Four words, guess it.
Four words.
(Li Naiwen and Guo Jingfei: 0 points)
It's over. Finished.
Zero points.
Finished.
No, his clothes rustle really loud.
Yes.
(Clothes revealed his location)
No, we just...
Let's just take a guess.
What is it?
I know.
What song?
What is it?
♪The road of life stretches for♪
♪Sweet dreams run just as long♪
(Correct answer)
A Chinese Ghost Story, right?
Yes.
Then go on humming.
The song's far from over.
(Speechless with anger)
Can you sing the notes?
You can, bro.
If he sings it and we hear,
we'll guess it.
And we'll win.
We can also guess.
(Direct mockery)
You even lost like that, zero points.
Let's not be so arrogant.
We can easily lose too.
Just be arrogant for a while.
Temporarily arrogant.
Whose turn now?
Lin Yi, come on.
(Describer: Lin Yi, Guesser: Wang Yuwen)
Okay.
Alright.
(Topic: Shoehorn)
(Close-distance warning)
(Escaped successfully)
Caught.
(Grabbing air)
It's you again.
(Whispering)
I want to put on...
Three characters.
Shoehorn.
Yes.
(Correct answer, 1 point)
Shoehorn.
So impressive.
You even guessed shoehorn.
(Eiffel Tower)
(Whispered)
Five characters.
Eiffel Tower.
Yes.
(Correct answer, 2 points)
So impressive.
(0-point scorer, anxious)
(Cramming at the last minute)
(Confidently speaking)
Before the exam, hurry to...
Five characters.
Cramming at the last minute.
(Correct answer, 3 points)
Yes.
So amazing.
(Anxious)
(Air freshener)
(Boldly speaking)
This room smells bad.
Spray something.
What?
(Anxious)
Insecticide.
That stink...
Deodorant.
Perfume.
Air freshener.
Yes.
(Correct answer, 4 points)
Something Chongqing people love to eat.
(Loud speaking)
That thing's...
(Eavesdropping)
What, what thing?
(Hot pot base)
Something you put in the pot.
Say it again.
How many characters?
When I go to Chongqing,
I'll bring you some.
Four characters.
Food.
(Countdown)
Bring what?
Bring some.
Hot pot base.
(Correct answer, 5 points)
Yes.
So impressive.
Impressive.
Very impressive.
(Wang Yuwen and Lin Yi: 5 points.)
(Perfect chemistry, Yili Yogurt Chewy Lemon is chewy)
Our chemistry is invincible.
(0-point partners)
Yes, look at Lin Yi and me.
We played pretty well originally.
What are you saying?
Yuwen and I also have great chemistry.
That's right, bro.
We two also have great chemistry.
Very...
So...
So it's them who are impressive, right?
(Describer: Chen Xingxu, Guesser: Song Qian,
Topic: Back-to-Back Hug)
A song by JJ Lin.
Back to Back.
Yes.
(Correct answer, 1 point)
(Only I have 0 points?)
What the heck?
A kind of breakfast.
But...
(Interrupting)
What?
(Separate, run away)
(Graceful dodge)
(A Pyrrhic victory)
It's me.
(High-difficulty dodge)
(Having gone through countless hardships,
striding with big steps)
(Looking forward to new hints)
A kind of breakfast.
(Didn't he just say it?)
(A kind of breakfast)
Five characters.
Right under my nose.
That's not right.
There's something.
(Escaped successfully)
Got you, right?
No.
(Cheerful)
A kind of breakfast.
Breakfast.
(Interrupting)
Right under my nose.
(Give me some information)
A kind of breakfast.
There is someone.
(Chen Xingxu is caught, mission over)
(Isn't ending a kind of relief?)
What thing?
It's just...
The description is just one sentence.
It's a kind of breakfast,
five characters.
Just five characters.
My brain has stopped working.
I don't know how to describe
these five characters.
It's a kind of breakfast.
Five characters.
Yes.
Chinese or Western?
They just didn't tell me what it is.
What is it?
Just that one sentence.
Sticky rice wrapped around fried dough.
Soy milk with fried dough.
Century egg and lean pork congee.
(Correct answer:
Century egg and lean pork congee)
Look.
(The great wisdom of the 0-point scorer)
Duck blood vermicelli soup
is also five characters.
Describe it in more detail.
If I described in detail,
I'm afraid they'd guess it.
(Also afraid I'd guess it?)
Buddy, what about two more characters?
If I said more,
my IQ would seem too low.
Not low, not at all.
I have experienced all these things.
It's in the past, okay?
Okay.
(Chen Xingxu and Song Qian: 1 point)
How is this game
played so badly by you guys?
Liu Yuning.
(So? How about that?)
Could you
give him a close-up shot?
Close-up.
Close-up shot.
There's already a close-up shot.
I don't understand, there's zero points.
Make enemies first, got it.
Come on.
Okay.
(Describer: Liu Yuning, Guesser: Sun Honglei,
Topic: Western Cowboy)
(Yuning's clever pass)
(The only zero-point scorer)
There's zero points.
Played so badly.
(Vowing to protect dignity)
It's me.
(Four characters, Got it)
(Preparing to make a move)
(Bye-bye)
(Dodge)
(Not hide and seek)
(Direction is messed up)
Who?
(Successfully disrupted the situation)
(A blank look)
(Close-distance warning)
(Bro, pay attention to me. I dodge)
Explosion.
What the heck?
Explode...
Explosion.
(The person involved
is completely unaware)
(Close-distance warning)
(Four characters,
telepathically transmitted)
I think he's on the ground.
They're on the ground.
(Vowing to protect dignity)
Nai,
don't stay on the floor.
You'll get stepped on.
(Continue telepathic transmission)
(Looking away)
(Bro, look at me)
(Close-distance warning)
(Pursuing relentlessly)
(Missed)
I can hear Liu Yuning panting.
Hurry!
Did you catch him?
(Liu Yuning is caught, mission over)
(Grabbing tightly)
Okay.
Alright.
Why are you kneeling?
Got him.
Nai.
Bro, you didn't guess?
(Innocent)
Zero points.
Bro.
How is this game
played so badly by you guys?
I don't understand, there's zero points.
We're all idiots.
Well...
Friends, how about this?
Four characters.
Western cowboy.
Wait, bro.
A Western cowboy's
gun is like this.
They way you did it...
Really.
You could at least wear a hat.
I wore one too,
but he completely ignored me.
He was playing hide and seek
with you guys.
We lost, we admit defeat.
I didn't guess this well.
(Didn't guess well, didn't guess at all)
Western cowboy.
Is a Western cowboy like this?
Like this.
That's actually true.
Right?
I can't believe you played so badly!
(Noob, this time
I'm talking about myself)
Everyone,
the first place
is undisputed.
(I think it's really great)
(First place: 5 points,
Wang Yuwen and Lin Yi)
The runner-up,
(Second place: 1 point, Chen Xingxu and Song Qian)
Chen Xingxu, Qian.
A narrow victory.
You're really not modest.
Right.
A narrow victory.
It was really narrow.
Right.
The competition for last place
is so fierce.
(Both teams have zero points)
How did you guys manage
to play this game like this, bro?
So bad!
Even zero points!
We're tied.
It's a draw.
Can't our two teams compete?
The IQ of these two,
and we tied with them?
How can we ever live this down?
Okay, come on.
Let's do it like this,
let's play a word game.
Any other questions?
A word game Let's bet our dignity.
Bet our dignity.
The loser has to
sincerely and wholeheartedly
say to the other side,
"Bro, I submit."
Okay, fine.
Okay.
Each team will guess one question.
If a teammate answers correctly,
they score.
If others answer correctly, no points,
and the question will be voided.
Okay, fine.
Come on, no problem.
Please, everyone.
Come on.
(All good helpers)
Little bro, you can do it!
Little sis, you can do it!
Come on, little sis, you can do it!
Bro, you can do it!
Come on.
(Describer: Guo Jingfei,
Guesser: Li Naiwen)
Three characters.
Come on.
Come on, bro.
(Surrounded)
How can this be? Look.
When you were guessing,
I didn't do this.
Go ahead.
Three characters.
Three characters, say it.
The American blockbuster
with those blue people.
Avatar.
I said it, Avatar.
I said it first.
Please, everyone.
I'm begging you.
He's really a master
at stirring things up.
When he plays himself,
he doesn't guess a single one.
You know, there's a phrase called
"When it's not my business,
I'm super strong."
When we fought it out,
you showed off your skills.
Xingxu, look at you.
Come on, I'll do it.
(Describer: Sun Honglei,
Guesser: Liu Yuning)
Three characters.
It's a name.
Andy Lau.
Jacky Cheung.
No.
It's a palace name.
Louvre.
It's in France.
Arc de Triomphe.
Versailles.
(Correct)
(Top-notch at answering)
(Impressed)
Xingxu.
Who said Versailles?
Right.
It has nothing to do with him.
No, it's fine as long
as it's not related to you.
Right.
That won't do, right?
I think it's okay.
As if drenched by rain.
Sour and refreshing.
That won't do, right?
I think it's okay.
As if bursting with power.
There's substance.
That won't do, right?
I think it's okay.
As if being soulmates.
Addictive.
(Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon
I chew, it works)
Let's add another one.
How about this?
Let's have Song Qian describe it.
We'll both guess.
Okay, come on.
We're having a penalty shootout.
Penalty shootout, right?
Right.
Penalty.
(Penalty shootout)
I'll start.
Say it.
How many characters?
Three characters.
I will wipe out every one of your...
Exterminate the nine clans.
I...
Xingxu.
What are you doing?
It's him again.
I just finished filming that.
Look, he doesn't even need
to stand in front.
He said from behind,
"Exterminate the nine clans."
Do you know what this feels like?
Two teams are in a penalty shootout,
and a spectator kicks the ball in.
Quick, come up with a question.
I really want to know
who between them will win.
Okay, just this one round.
(Ultimate showdown)
Three characters.
The third character
is related to this.
Shoe.
No, the thing inside this.
Foot.
Flatfoot.
Athlete's foot.
The first part is...
What the heck?
The first character is this.
Crawl.
Dog paddle.
Digging.
Dig.
Pick.
Related to this.
(Dig ? foot)
Dig.
Poach.
(Sun Honglei and Liu Yuning win)
Right.
Goal!
Paris Saint-Germain.
Where's the FIFA World Cup Trophy?
Earth, quick...
How come the third place
is acting like champions?
Look at how excited you get.
Awarding the third place.
They are fourth place.
You stand a little shorter.
Then call me bro.
When facing Yuning,
no need to be shorter.
Just stand normally.
No, let's do this.
We'll be on both sides.
It's okay to be on both sides.
Let's step back a bit, bro.
Okay.
Ready, go.
Bro, I submit.
Not satisfied.
It just didn't feel heartfelt.
Well, you guys feel it.
Do you think it can pass? Okay?
I thought it was
a bit sarcastic just now.
Sarcastic.
Right.
Really?
Look.
Now that you say it,
I think it really was like that.
Come on, be sincere.
Be sincere.
Can we two be sincere?
Yes.
Okay.
Come on.
Ready.
Ready, go.
Don't put on that air.
I should put on an air.
Come on.
(With a serious expression)
Bro,
I submit.
That's passed.
Pretty good.
How is it?
It's okay.
This is very accurate, bro.
(There's a benchmark now)
You need to be more accurate, bro.
It can't be the same as Naiwen's.
Can't repeat the performance.
(Increasing the difficulty)
Come on, okay.
Fei.
Give Fei a bold and capital.
Bold and capital.
I'm especially sincere.
Come on.
Bro...
How come there's choreography?
What are you dodging for?
I wanted...
I wanted to add some choreography.
To make it a bit watchable,
saying "I submit."
This movement won't work.
Come on, okay.
- You lost the vibe like that.
- Yeah.
(Older and younger buddy duo)
It feels like a sneak attack on bro.
I wanted to change the choreography.
I wanted to be original.
You know?
Let's congratulate our winners again.
Lin Yi, Yuwen.
No sense of achievement.
Not us.
He's been raising his hand
for a long time. He's here.
Not us.
Come on.
Let's bring out the Opera Cake
as a reward for the winners.
This Opera Cake
was created in 1955.
It's called
the ultimate coffee chocolate.
Coffee chocolate is my favorite.
Do you want me to feed you, bro?
Don't.
You, a third-place,
what right do you have?
I can't even smell it?
How is it?
Describe it.
What's the taste?
Is it sweet?
Sweet.
Lin Yi.
Is it delicious?
Delicious.
Besides sweetness, what other flavor?
It's quite smooth.
Quite soft.
A bit of caramel flavor.
And a bit of coffee liquid taste.
It has that evaporating feeling.
Wait.
Look at the group of guys here.
All want to take a bite.
It feels like they're about
to pounce at it.
Quick.
Quick, give them the dessert.
I also want to be called bro.
I submit.
Quick, bring it over.
Alright, easy come, easy go.
Yeah, it's fine.
We're all like this.
Everyone has it.
Come on.
Okay.
Let's distribute it.
This is delicious.
This one.
Bro.
Come on, baby.
Alright.
Is it far?
Not far, to the Seine River.
It'll take just a few minutes.
As long as there's no traffic.
(Heading to the Seine River)
I've been praising you everywhere.
I suppose you already know.
(Shy)
I don't know.
I heard you and Zhao Jinmai...
I heard you went
to show off to Zhao Jinmai.
It spread so fast.
I told her when I visited her
the other day.
My eyes and ears are everywhere.
(My connections are everywhere)
(Seeking truth)
But you said I’m smart.
Did you mean it?
Of course.
Really.
(Now intelligence is recognized.)
- Then I... - I told them that but they don't believe it.
Only I can see how smart you are.
(There are always talented horses,
but not always true judges.)
(Arriving at the Seine River)
We're here.
Let's get off.
Okay.
Why are you wearing a wool vest?
(New sweater)
When you wear this,
(Old dad)
you look exactly like an old dad.
I admit that.
No.
I think more like an old mom.
Old mom.
- This is my own clothes.
- Don't you think so?
I'm really cold.
I didn't bring thick clothes.
But this one...
It doesn't block the wind.
Warm.
(Slightly warm)
Now it's just warm.
Well...
You...
You should buy a pink one.
Right.
(Lei’s signature pink
fashionable color)
(You’ll get it once you wear it)
Let's get on the boat.
Let's go.
Come on.
(You first)
♪Go, go, go. Let's go♪
Be careful.
We suddenly arrived
at the other side of the Eiffel Tower.
(Northwest side of the Eiffel Tower)
Right.
Look at the clouds.
So pretty.
So big.
So beautiful.
It's very relaxing.
I see our boat.
Which one?
The one right ahead.
I see it.
So big.
(Boarding the cruise ship)
Walk the red carpet.
Go.
Hello.
This is my Aunt Guo.
(A sudden persona)
He
brought my aunt's clothes.
I quickly knitted a sweater
and put it on.
(Already in character)
You brought this?
Right.
(The only one wearing a coat)
(Jealous)
Look how smart he is.
Now you know what "old money style" is.
Now you know what "old money" is.
He's been around here for so long.
Oh, I see.
(Very familiar)
He knows the weather here.
Look at me.
I could only knit a sweater myself.
(Taking it to heart)
Wait.
If you're cold,
I'll ask them to bring
some clothes
from my house.
(Can't lose the duke status outside)
Do you mean Tianjin?
My home is nearby.
(Zero-frame performance)
Just a stone's throw away.
He's a duke.
(At a slight disadvantage)
(Who isn't a duke here?)
Bring my boat over here.
I'm going back.
I can't talk with these people.
(Completely triggered)
We're ready to set sail.
What scenery is there
on the Seine River?
Let's have our tour guide.
introduce them.
Hello, everyone.
We are now on the Seine River
(Official guide of the French museum)
of the romantic Paris.
(Zuli Shu)
This river
originates from Burgundy, France.
The word "Seine"
comes
from a goddess
in Gaulish mythology.
(Seine River is one of the most important rivers in northern France, flowing from southeast to northwest through the heart of the country.)
(It has played a huge role)
This river was once
(in French history,)
the largest shipping channel
(culture, and economy.)
in French history.
Its total length in France
is over 700 kilometers long,
while the Paris section
is less than 20 kilometers.
The earliest Seine River
cruise experience
dates back to the British Queen.
On this river,
there are over thirty bridges.
Along the banks, you’ll see
the oldest one.
(Pont Neuf connects both banks of the Seine and Île de la Cité.)
It was the first bridge without buildings
(It is the oldest stone arch bridge in Paris.)
and residences.
(Construction started in 1578 and completed in 1607 under Henry IV.)
So, it's called Pont Neuf (New Bridge).
(It's listed as a UNESCO World Heritage Site)
Now the bridge you see
is a inflatable bridge transformed
by the French local artist JR.
(Temporary inflatable installation The Cave of Pont Neuf)
You see the bridge body is white
(To pay homage)
and black.
(to Christo and Jeanne-Claude’s 1985 artwork The Pont Neuf Wrapped.)
Actually, when you get closer,
(JR used giant inflatable "cave" covering the historic bridge)
you'll find it look like simulated rocks.
(in June 2026, turning this Paris landmark)
(into a space between urban landscape, geology, theater, and illusion.)
That's interesting.
Over there
is Pont de Bir-Hakeim,
where Inception
was filmed.
The Metro Line 6
runs above,
and pedestrians walk below.
(Movie Inception)
It's pretty cute.
Look, many people over there.
- Hello.
Hello.
Look at the pigeon.
There's an echo.
This bridge is really beautiful.
So beautiful.
The people above will wave at you.
The one in white.
At night, every hour on the hour,
the Eiffel Tower lights up
with 20,000 bulbs,
becoming a golden tower.
So beautiful.
Paris at sunset.
Another boat is coming.
Hello.
Honglei!
I'm quite famous in France.
Noticed it?
(Beaming with joy)
Clouds.
Sunset.
What a wonderful life.
So worth it.
Life is truly worth it.
Let's go inside the cabin.
Let's go.
Go downstairs.
The boat is so fast.
Because our boats are passing each other
Right, head-on rush.
Enjoying a warm moment
in the breeze on the Seine.)
We're very lucky today.
It just rained earlier,
so when we took photos,
the sky turned blue
and the clouds became pink.
It was absolutely beautiful.
The sky is very clear today.
We've experienced all four seasons.
(Sunny, rain, after rain)
If it snows later, that'll be something.
(Hail)
- It even hailed today - Right.
Also,
Paris is one of the cities
with the highest density
of film locations in the world.
In Before Sunset, the main characters
looked out at Notre-Dame from the Seine.
On December 28, 1895,
the world's first film,
Arrival of a Train,
was born in France.
marking the beginning of cinema.
Films like Arrival of a Train,
Workers Leaving the Factory,
The Sprinkler Sprinkled,
and artistic and avant-garde cinema
were all born in France.
The next task
has a little to do with acting.
It involves professional stuff again.
You can perform a musical.
(Zero-second transformation)
So that's how it is.
(Like meeting a soulmate through music)
I don't know what's wrong with you.
(The acting bug is strong)
Next,
(Acting relay)
you'll be divided into two groups.
Each group sends three people to compete.
Two of them act,
and one serves as the guide.
The guide leads the actors
to say three predetermined lines.
After guessing all three correctly,
they also need to guess
a final improvised line
from the other team.
The team with the shortest time wins.
Understood.
- What are you saying?
- What are you talking about?
He didn't understand.
(Mouthpiece)
Frankly speaking, I said it for nothing.
Let's split into teams first.
What about this?
You two choose from us six guys.
Okay.
(Whisper Word Guessing)
Yuwen and Lin Yi are partners.
(The winning team has the right to choose)
Xingxu and I form one.
Then we'll choose the remaining
(The remaining)
two groups of guys.
I dare not choose.
I have to say something.
(Raising objections)
Why are we
- the leftovers?
- Why should we be chosen?
Because we are third and fourth place.
(Raising a question)
(Withdrawing the question)
Come on.
First and second place, you pick.
Anyone want to fight for it?
Anyone who wants to be in our group?
So what are your advantages, girls?
Okay.
(Turning passive into active)
Who picks who/?
(Is this right?)
How did the situation...
A sudden reversal.
A sudden reversal?
Be honest.
- You really want me to be honest, Nai?
- Yes.
Choose
the person I want?
I want Honglei's group.
(Yuwen's choice)
(Competitive spirit ignited)
She looks down on us.
We have to prove it to them.
(Not afraid)
Beat them.
I just think Honglei's acting
is the best.
(I'll be blunt)
I admit it.
(The competitive spirit is not much)
Wang Yuwen.
(What's happening?)
I also admit it.
(A false alarm)
Okay.
My face is all red.
(Grouping complete: Li Naiwen,
Guo Jingfei, Song Qian, Chen Xingxu.)
(Sun Honglei, Liu Yuning,
Lin Yi, Wang Yuwen.)
Our captain is in charge of planning.
Okay.
- Let's look at the prompt.
- Okay, come on.
(Scenario: A domineering CEO and the daughter of his family’s enemy)
Like Romeo and Juliet, right?
(secretly flew to France for a date,)
Roles:
(caught by the mother on the spot. She goes berserk.)
Domineering CEO.
Daughter of the family enemy.
(Guide: Overbearing CEO's mother)
The guide is the mother-in-law, right?
It's to guide out that keyword.
(Sitting back to watch the joke)
Then it's definitely Guo Jingfei.
(This round's designated lines:
True love, I was wrong, I have a clear conscience.)
It will only get harder later.
Then let's just do this one.
Okay.
(Eager to try)
Do you want
to start the first shot?
(Seeing through)
- I'll play the mother. - You want to play the mother?
Right.
I know you want to play the mother.
Because I'm guiding,
all three of you can guess.
Right?
Okay.
You three.
Come on.
Then we'll go first.
What does this mean?
(Prescribed lines card)
Mention this keyword.
I'm truly in love with him.
(This round's lines: True love,
I was wrong, I have a clear conscience.)
We have to give them an extra
spicy and numbing word.
(Discussing the ultimate line)
For example, something like
Hainan coconut juice.
Something completely unrelated.
That's also a direction.
Here it comes.
We have already started.
(Already in character)
Come on, three, two, one, start.
(Chen Xingxu, the domineering CEO.
Song Qian, the daughter of the rival family.)
Look.
Quite beautiful, right?
I can't stand it.
(Deeply captivated)
I told you
not to bring me to France.
What if your mother finds out?
She'll be angry.
It's fine.
My dad won't find out.
(It should be mom.)
I've chartered the whole boat.
Even if she comes by speedboat,
she can't catch up.
This is our secret trip.
There’s no way they’ll find out.
We just flew here this morning.
And
We watch the night view here tonight.
How could she possibly know?
Indeed.
I still have jet lag.
What should we do?
(Waiting for the right moment to enter)
It's fine.
No problem.
I still think
we should buy tickets and fly back.
What if your mother...
What if your father...
What if your father and mother...
(Holding back)
What did my mother do to my father?
What if he takes
away your inheritance rights?
Impossible.
Alright.
stop telling me
about your achievements.
(Did I say it?)
I'm tired of hearing them.
I admit you're excellent.
But...
I can't let you
give up your whole family for me.
It's okay.
(Love this, binge-watch all day)
You are my whole world.
Take a good look.
What are you doing?
(This round's lines: True love,
I was wrong, I have a clear conscience.)
Dad?
I'm your mom.
(Guo Jingfei,
the domineering CEO's mother.)
Mom?
I'm your mother.
Maybe my male hormones are a bit high,
(Trying not to laugh)
a bit strong.
That’s because you two made me angry.
You didn't expect me
to come so quickly, did you?
No.
Listen to me.
This has nothing to do with her.
Get lost!
No.
This matter is absolutely because of me.
Mom.
No, I mean, ma'am.
Wait, you can't just change my identity.
(Changing the words in advance)
She chooses to escalate the conflict.
(Totally getting it)
How many times have I told you
we have a family feud?
How can you be with him?
(You, him)
(Ma'am, you?)
(Mom, you?)
(It's a total mess)
You're my mom.
Which path are you going to take?
- You're my mom.
- Aren't you a domineering CEO?
(What's the problem?)
(Brilliant)
I am a domineering CEO.
(Domineering CEO's mother.)
(Mother of the domineering CEO.)
(Reviewing the prompt)
A domineering CEO.
The daughter of a family enemy.
(Smoothly getting back into character)
I've told you so many times.
How can you be with her?
Ma'am.
Don't scold him.
It's all my fault.
I'm curious.
What's her background?
No matter what her background is,
whatever feud we have,
she is the woman I love the most.
(True love, close to the line.)
That's not what you said.
Well...
The most...
Not the most.
After last time I heard it,
I just felt that you
could get married right away.
How come you've changed to another one?
(what's the plot?)
I didn't change.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
So, you...
Don't explain to her now.
Tell me first.
Back then,
(Answer the prompt first)
when you described that girl back then,
what kind of love was it?
(Say it boldly)
That girl you described.
True love.
Right?
He said she was his true love.
Yes.
(A quick learner)
That's right.
I did say she was my true love.
(Let me interject)
Miss,
a man like this...
- He tells every girl she’s his true love.
- Mom, you are my mom.
(Sneaking a peek at the next line)
Can you trust him?
No.
Look at you.
You tell every girl
that she is your true love.
Tell me,
what should you say to her now?
Three words.
(The guidance is on point)
I'm sorry.
(Think again)
No.
I love you.
The first word is right.
And then?
(Then what?)
I...
(Think differently)
Don't continue being a fraud.
Things like "I love you"?
Are you still trying to deceive?
I...
I believe you.
(What a love-struck fool)
What the heck?
I believe you.
(Are my teammates trustworthy?)
(Deep in character)
It's me who doesn't believe you, okay?
(Please look at me)
You have to believe me.
Why it's you believe me?
(Seriously. Careful.)
After you say this,
this relationship should end,
and you can go find the next true love.
Do you understand?
Let's break up.
(Finally got some new progress)
- Just say that. - Don't.
No.
It's almost there.
Then what do you have to say?
(Waiting for "I was wrong")
I...
- I...
- Aren't you good at guessing?
Aren't you good at guessing?
Aren't you my good son?
I do.
(I don't know what's wrong with you.)
Love-struck fool.
When you were little,
I made you play the piano.
Yes.
(With a mother's earnest heart)
You could never play it right.
What did you often say to me?
I was wrong.
Can't you say this?
Right.
Look at you.
The girl you choose.
The only advantage...
(Mother-in-law's approval)
She's smart.
(Smart and beautiful)
The next generation
has hope.
I'm starting to be swayed now.
Starting to speak the truth.
Speaking from the heart.
(Preparing to guide the next line)
You.
You...
(Focused on acting)
Mom, listen to me.
She truly is the woman I love the most.
So, no matter what you say,
or how our feud stands,
I will never leave her.
Very good, child.
(This part is over)
The feud of our generation
belongs to us.
It's in the past.
For your generation,
if you can say such words,
achieve a four-word phrase,
(4 characters)
I think,
I will support you.
(Achieve 4 characters, Mom supports me.)
(This round is in the bag)
Love is stronger than gold.
(The opponent's strength
is totally reassuring.)
You two...
In your current state,
you can't have a baby right away.
Got it?
Use
your mind.
I'll give you a little more hint.
(Hold steady. I'm here.)
Well, touching your conscience and feeling,
I...
(Got it?)
(Same look of confusion)
(Try again)
Well.
Today,
you and her,
don't think of me and your dad.
- Don't care of the previous feud.
- Right.
I often consult
your father
- how much money was earned this year.
- Okay.
This word "consult".
(Key point: consult)
Describe it with another word.
(Kids, do you understand?)
- Have a clear conscience.
Very good, children.
You can have a baby right away.
(Being a supportive adult)
Okay.
Ma'am.
(Relieved)
(Generating the ultimate line)
(Here goes)
Mom.
(The ultimate line is coming)
You come.
(Ultimate line: Kong Rong Gives Away the Pear.)
Mom.
(Already in character)
(Ultimate line: Kong Rong Gives Away the Bigger Pears
Guide: Song Qian.)
I know
you're sincere to me.
Yes.
(Eagerly testing the line)
Do I have to be sincere to you too?
(That's not necessary.)
Auntie, I know you have given him
and his brother
a very good upbringing since childhood.
- Yes.
But...
But
actually,
there's something I've been holding
in my heart and wanting to say.
(The situation is delicate)
Actually,
his brother was my first love.
(What kind of plot is this?)
(Mother, do you understand?)
So, I think
since your family upbringing is so good,
why not let him...
(Let me?)
(Let him?)
Leave now.
Why not let him take me...
Scatter to the sea?
Scatter to the sea.
There is a four-character idiom
(Key info: four-character idiom)
I believe
Got it.
(Got it)
you must teach him when he was little.
You might also make him
learn some
four-character idioms, Chinese classics,
and some history.
Yes, I made him learn.
I didn't learn much.
No, you...
Boy, it's okay.
I have experienced all of this.
Don't be afraid.
Speak slowly. Don't rush.
Think about it too.
(I'm thinking)
For example,
compare me
to a very crisp, fragrant, sweet,
and good-looking apple.
Or,
the apple's friend is...
Pear.
(Got something)
- Kong Rong Gives Away the Pear.
(Guess the ultimate line)
Song Qian, have you lost your mind?
What does this have to do
(The mother-in-law is furious)
with Kong Rong Gives Away the Pear?
Isn't this just giving me away to him?
(Fine)
Get divorced?
[*"Divorce" and "Pear" sound the same]
Nice.
Not bad.
Very impressive.
This is quite fun.
It's kind of interesting.
- Nice.
- How is it?
- Very good.
- I played pretty well, right?
Yes.
Okay.
It's over.
It feels like our team lost.
Impossible.
We...
How long did they take to finish?
(Song Qian's team time: 14m 20s)
14 minutes.
We'll get it done in four minutes.
Come on, your turn.
(Let's see the strength)
It's your turn.
Okay.
(Scenario: The innkeeper receives)
a couple who are having a quarrel.
(a martial arts couple having a quarrel,
and one of them is your ex)
(Actors: A martial arts couple)
Okay.
(Guide: Innkeeper)
(Required lines: The Two Fiends)
Okay.
(Pigeon Post, Rob the cradle)
Let's think of the lines first.
You do it.
I'm not doing it. You do it.
Okay, then I'll be the innkeeper.
You two are the couple.
Okay, you're the guide, right?
(Trusting Yuning)
It feels like it'll be very fast.
Okay, come on.
One of us is his ex, right?
Which one of us is his ex?
No, it has to be me.
Come on. Having a quarrel, right?
Having a quarrel.
(Fictional scenario,
please do not take it seriously)
(Liu Yuning as the innkeeper, male)
Honey.
(Lin Yi as martial arts couple, male
Yuwen as martial arts couple, female)
My Love.
(Aha)
Shall we
eat?
(Leave a tiger)
[*Sound like "Shall we eat?" in Chinese]
Behind?
[*Idiom: Leave a tiger behind]
(What plot is this?)
Behind?
(Quickly playing along)
But we don't have...
No travel money.
I want to eat something.
(Let's walk towards the inn)
Go
to the inn.
(Friendly reminder)
(Lines: The Two Fiends, Pigeon Post,
Rob the cradle)
- Not far away, is there
- Not far away...
an inn?
Inn?
I don't care.
You don't care?
Then I shall quarrel.
(Both have a little temper)
If you quarrel, I shall leave home.
I shall sleep outside tonight.
Then I shall follow.
(Having waited impatiently
for a long time)
Knock, knock, knock.
You two,
are you here for a meal or a room?
It's you?
(Old acquaintance, Steve,
Old acquaintance)
How is it you?
How could it be?
Since we parted last time...
(Who are you, sir?)
Excuse me.
Who is this?
I don't know him.
(Enjoying it)
My Love.
Aha!
Why couldn't you suppress that smirk
since you stepped through the door?
I'm naturally a smiley person.
Naturally a smiley person.
Then your luck shouldn't be too bad.
(Winning by having more gags)
Honey, I really admire your wisdom.
Do you still remember me?
I...
Of course, I remember you.
- You?
- My Yuning.
Your Yuning?
(Front-row spectator)
(Embarrassed)
(Panicked)
Did I let it slip?
How many Yunings do you have?
(Jealous)
Yuning,
you are my true love.
(The king of puns can't stand this)
This isn't good, is it?
Then do you remember,
(Starting to guide the Two Fiends)
back then,
what the martial world called us
- when we were together back then?
- The Condor couple.
No.
Immortals...
(Denying it)
No.
(Thinking)
In the martial world,
- there's a famous
- Stop talking.
title.
Guess.
(Designated answer)
That's right.
- We are the Two Fiends.
- That's right.
You...
(Totally awesome)
(Highlight moment)
We really are the Two Fiends.
We have to make that kind of laugh.
The Two Fiends.
- Hahaha.
(Don't understand but respect it)
Okay.
Next.
What else do you have?
Truly impressive.
But I remember
(Continue to guide)
I sent you many letters before.
(Receiving info: sending letters)
The method I used was the most advanced
method in the martial world.
Pigeon Post?
That's right.
(The Two Awesome Fiends)
What?
(What?)
No wonder you fed me
pigeon soup every day.
So, it turns out
there's this kind of thing.
Awesome.
It's blown up.
(No competition, only admiration)
I see you are handsome and dashing,
a truly renowned
young hero in the martial world.
(Loves to hear it, keep talking)
You can continue.
You are a...
Perfect match of beauty and talent.
A perfect what...
No.
Jackals, wolves, tigers, and leopards.
[*Sound like "perfect match" in Chinese]
No.
Mutual affection, or a perfect match,
either works.
Okay.
But if you're with me,
then it's called...
Birds of a feather?
No.
In my heart, those five characters,
if it's...
If you're with him,
it's a perfect match.
If you're with me, it is...
(Willing to self-destruct)
Five characters?
It's that very hurtful phrase, actually.
It's a pity it's not you.
No.
It's describing me as an animal.
(Animal)
Is it a relatively negative animal?
I am an animal.
(Key info: animal + plant)
You are a plant.
A kind of fresh flower
(Flower.)
- stuck
- Stuck
- in cow dung?
That's a bit too hurtful.
It's an animal,
but not the animal's
excrement.
(I'm impressed by you two)
Okay.
Then, it's
- related to cabbage and pigs.
- No!
Is it related to a toad and a swan?
(What a ruckus)
(Laughing so hard he loses his voice)
It's the animal you just mentioned.
What is cow dung?
It's this kind of animal.
(Can't be other animals)
A cow...
You and him are a perfect match.
If you're with me,
I'm so old, right?
(Gone through too much
to guess the answer)
- You're so old...
I know.
What is it?
You are
- robbing the cradle!
- That's right!
Yes.
(Ultimate line)
(The ultimate line is coming)
Thrown to...
What?
The pigeon from the Pigeon Post.
The Pigeon Post was for her.
For her.
- Pigeon Post.
- Was it for me?
Right.
(Sitting back and watching the show)
(Ultimate line: Durian milk)
So, next,
do you have anything to say?
Honey.
Hey.
Huh?
(Steve)
(Oh, my big mouth)
I'm sorry.
I just suddenly recalled
our past.
Are you okay?
Honey,
for the time we've been together,
we actually
aren't very compatible.
Incompatible in what?
(This tea is piping hot)
(Don't panic)
For example,
there's something I really love to eat,
but you really dislike.
(There's food I can't accept?)
Yay!
What is it?
A kind of fruit that when eaten,
you absolutely can't stand it.
Then I know.
What she dislikes the most is durian.
(It has to be Yuning)
Correct.
- Is it correct?
- Correct.
Is it correct?
(A wild guess)
No.
(Not yet fully correct)
I almost withdrew.
I almost
wanted to let you two be together.
You two are so tall.
(Tall men in the martial world)
You should usually be
eating pretty well.
In our ancient times,
it's actually quite rare.
What did you just say?
Eat what?
Beef.
Yes, it's this kind of animal.
It's something produced from its body,
but not that kind of stuff.
It's just...
Cow dung?
(Off-site interference)
He doesn't like to eat cow dung.
No.
It seems
you really love to eat it?
(That extra remark)
My Love,
are you trying to say
the name of a type of food?
This thing needs to be
squeezed.
Durian milk, right?
Yes.
You don't even understand her.
Right?
You understand her better.
Yes, give her to this old cow,
(Act out the full scene)
okay?
You shall
eat this grass.
(Congratulations to this old couple)
Okay, I'll eat it.
I accept your concession.
- Good.
Great.
Everyone,
winning or losing isn't important.
Right.
But there's always a winner and a loser.
Then again...
The team with the shorter time is
Yuwen's team.
Congratulations.
(Sun Honglei, Liu Yuning,
Lin Yi, Wang Yuwen)
(Won with a time of 8m 20s)
Totally won.
Winning or losing isn't important,
but we're doing better.
We are second now, right?
(A good attitude
determines a man's life)
Right?
What else would it be?
We're doing better.
(Thrilling)
The game just now was too thrilling.
What do you think?
[*"Think" sounds like "Chew"]
I think it's pretty good.
(Raising the stakes)
Let's raise the stakes and try.
Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon
thrilling moment.
(Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon Challenge)
One person spins the wheel,
and the other calls stop
within three seconds.
Aligning the avatar
with the chewy lemon is a success.
(Heart-racing)
Three successes to win the chewy lemon.
(Playing so big)
The penalty is eating a lemon.
(Round 1)
Go.
Stop.
(Almost)
(Failed)
Failed once.
(Tension maxed out)
Are we really going to eat a lemon?
(Round 2)
One, two, three.
Go.
(Blind stop)
(Finally)
Congratulations, Yi.
(Actually, just kidding)
(Starting to make excuses)
I was just a little unlucky.
I need to drink a chewy lemon
to replenish my luck.
(Chewing)
(Replenishing luck)
Okay.
(I can do it again)
My luck is coming.
(Round 3)
One, two, three.
Go.
(Staring intently)
Stop.
(Successfully hooked)
(Cheers)
Thanks, Honglei.
Okay.
(Thanks to the chewy lemon)
Finally got my favorite chewy lemon.
(Delicious, love it)
Delicious.
I love it.
(Next Episode Preview)
Among the four people in each group,
three need to use their acting skills
to fully cover for their teammate.
Three scheming people.
This is next-level.
Name the three most handsome parts
of Naiwen.
Hairstyle, philtrum,
(Secret)
Is this what you think
or what he thinks?
I can even
come up with a name for their team.
Just call them "The Unbreakables".
Ask her which year and which drama
she collaborated with Liu Yuning on.
I know all of this.
She said she doesn't
even want to think about it.
Amazing.
Everyone has their own strengths.
I think it's Yuwen.
(Who is actually acting?)
Sino-French fusion cuisine
creative showdown.
There's no knife?
Take it out,
our cleaver.
You stole our knife.
The pot is gone too. So how could we...
Steal the pot.
Give us back our pot.
This side is already burnt
on the bottom.
It's not. Where is it burnt?
I need to do some carving.
I need to show some real skill.
(Which team's cooking is better?)
Everyone will receive
a hidden mission unique to themselves.
Is it the kind
where you embarrass others,
- or where others embarrass you?
- It's where everyone has a hard time.
What is this?
Put on makeup yourself?
Jingfei, your mission is so shameful.
Are the pants worn too?
The pants can't be pulled down.
Nai.
(What exactly is their hidden mission?)
(A battle)
(for the inheritance of Vaux-le-Vicomte)
(quietly begins.)
Using dance to challenge the other heirs
to a head-to-head showdown.
They are bound to lose.
This won't fall off.
The desire to win is extremely strong.
You've got some skills.
I misjudged you before.
No, it's not necessary.
You can't repeat a move
that's already been done, right?
(Who will win?)
This round of the test
is related to how well
everyone knows each other.
Can you really guess what I'll say?
If I wanted to guess.
Can I curse?
Stop.
I'm the baby.
Who is calling whom?
Xingxu.
My son,
I am about to play the male lead
in an idol drama.
That's great!
The way you say it sounds so sarcastic.
(Here it comes)
One day, I suddenly received
an invitation to I Am a Singer Too.
Great, do I need to sing?
It should be like
he called Zhou Ye.
You can't slander my singing skills.
(Who has the highest level
of understanding of each other?)
(Extra Episode preview)
7s Heartbeat Charades, trial round.
I guarantee you'll win with me.
The pressure is too much.
Left hand on top.
Left hand on the head.
Right arm slightly bent.
No, bent outward.
What kind of move is this?
Body suddenly shudders.
Fall down.
Raise your eyes.
Look at me with deep affection.
(Deeply affection?)
And then...
Hahaha!
I'm too strong.
Do you understand?
You said it, but it's like
you said nothing.
- We already guessed it.
- We all guessed it. You're no good.
Your Majesty.
No, you've got it backwards.
Retired Emperor?
[*Your Majesty in reverse]
(Which group will win?)
(Post-credits scene)
Have you seen this movie?
I've seen it.
What are they doing?
They are dancing.
Is that guy eating hair?
No.
It's just that kind
of a deeply tender and languid feeling.
Okay.
Nail it.
Where are your ears?
Where are my ears?
Lin Yi, don't turn around.
If he turns around,
it'll be exposed. Right.
What do you mean by not turning around?
It's like this.
Like this?
- Why not let him turn around?
- If he turns, we can see his legs.
I thought...
Okay.
It's a bit dry with just the two of us.
I can go borrow something,
I can go
to that pole over there.
What are you doing at the pole?
I can just lean on it,
and then I can do this.
I've never felt Paris was so beautiful.
You're too pretentious.
I've never thought
Paris was as beautiful as it is today.
Don't move.
Sorry, I mistook you for someone else.
It really doesn't look like you.
Come back.
Honestly,Don't say it,
if he's ten years older,
and 20 pounds heavier,
(I think it's okay)
he really looks like you.
I am...
[*Foreign language]
Hello.
That little girl
also has a necklace.
How to wear it?
Necklace.
Okay, come on.
Let's do it.
You can wear it as a bow tie.
Why do I feel like
Yuning is going to choke me?
So romantic.
I can't stand it.
I feel like we're here to film a drama.
It's true. We're back on set.